[
    {
        "question": "Which of the following are the advantages of React.js?",
        "choices": ["React.js can increase the application's performance with Virtual DOM.", "React.js is easy to integrate with other frameworks such as Angular, BackboneJS since it is only a view library.", "React.js can render both on client and server side.", "All of the above"],
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "What of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
        "choices": ["Original DOM", "Virtual DOM", "Both A and B.", "None of the above."],
        "answer": "Both A and B."
    },
    {
        "question": " How many ways of defining your variables in ES6?",
        "choices": ["1", "3", "4", "5"],
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a state in React?",
        "choices": ["A permanent storage.", "Internal storage of the component.", "External storage of the component.", "None of the above."],
        "answer": "Internal storage of the component."
    },
    {
        "question": "What does ES6 stand for?",
        "choices": ["ECMAScript 6", "ECMA 6", "ECMAJavaScript 6", "EJavaScript 6"],
        "answer": "ECMAScript 6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the use of the create-react-app command in the React.js application?",
        "choices": ["It is used to update a React app.", "It is used to create a new React app.", "It is used to install dependencies.", "None of the above."],
        "answer": "It is used to create a new React app."
    },
    {
        "question": "The property in CSS used to change the background color of an element is",
        "choices": ["bgcolor", "color", "background-color", "All of the above"],
        "answer": "background-color"
    },
    {
        "question": "The HTML attribute used to define the internal stylesheet is",
        "choices": ["<style>", "style", "<link>", "<script>"],
        "answer": "<style>"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following property is used as the shorthand property for the padding properties?",
        "choices": ["padding-left", "padding-right", "padding", "All of the above"],
        "answer": "padding"
    },
    {
        "question": "The CSS property used to specify the transparency of an element is",
        "choices": ["opacity", "filter", "visibility", "overlay"],
        "answer": "opacity"
    }
]